我是哪里不对  我看起来不够有趣吗
What is it about me? Do I not look fun enough?
我是有哪里讨人厌吗
Is there something repellent about me?
派对好玩吗
How was the party?
太糟糕了  有个女人简直把我当空气了
It couldn't have been worse. A woman literally passed through me.
我有那么讨人厌吗
What is it? Am I hideously unattractive?
不  你非常讨人喜欢
No,you are not. You are very attractive.
我也有过相同的经历
You know what, I go through the exact same thing.
每当我体重稍有增长  就开始质疑一切了
Every time I put on a little weight, I start questioning everyting.
你说我变胖了
I've put on weight?
你要...
Did you want to...?
不  不是体重  说绝缘体比较恰当
No, not weight. More like insulation.
钱德勒  我正好没工作  迫切需要做点事情
Chandler, I'm unemployed and in dire need of a project.
你要不要锻炼  我可以重塑你的体型
Ya wanna work out? I can remake you.
我很想  但或许会妨碍我那些无所事事的时间
I would,but that might get in the way of my lying-around time.
拜托啦
Please?
别推托了  让她试试
Come on,let her do it!
好吧
All right.
但我穿上紧身衣后胸部比你大的话  我就不练了
But if we put on spandex and my boobs are bigger than yours, I'm goin' home.
你的胸部不大
Your boobs are fine.
听着  我刚才不该乱说话的
I never should have said anything.
过来  过来
Come here. Come here!
双手都合不起来了
Can't make hands meet!
好  开始吧
OK. Let's do it!
怎么了
What?
没什么  只是没看过你穿紧身裤而已
Nothing. Just never seen your little stretchy pants before.
我去换衣服
And we're changing.
加油  再做五个
Come on,give me five more!
-再做五个  -不要
- Five more! - No.
再做五个就露胸部给你看
Five more and I'll flash you.
一
One...
二
...two...
二个半
...two and a half.
好了  给我看一边吧
OK. Just show me one of them.
她疯了
She's insane!
那个女人疯了
The woman is insane.
上班前  上班后  上班中
It's before work, it's after work, it's during work.
她叫我在公司做收臀运动
She's got me doing butt-clenches at my desk.
现在他们再不肯送邮件给我了
And now they won't bring me my mail anymore.
菲比  你昨晚跟史考特怎么样
Hey Phoebs, how'd it go with Scott last night?
不错  带他去了一家浪漫的餐厅
It was nice. Took him to a romantic restaurant...
点了香槟  很好
...ordered champagne. Nice.
那家伙还是不行动吗
The guy still won't put out?
对  零蛋  没行动
Nope. Zilch. Nothing.
真遗憾  菲比
Sorry, Pheebs.
我不在乎放慢节奏
Look,I don't mind taking it slow.
我很喜欢他
I like him a lot.
他这个人很有趣  也很贴心
He's really interesting,and he's really sweet.
他为什么那么矜持
Why won't he give it up?
或许他开的车跟我们反向
Maybe he drives his car on the other side of the road.
你懂我的意思吧
If you know what I mean.
不懂  他又不是英国人
No. What do you mean? He's not British.
他或许是同性恋
Maybe he's gay.
不  这倒不是问题
No. I don't think that's the problem.
因为我们前几天去跳舞
Because we went dancing the other night...
他紧紧抱住我  还有他凝视我眼睛的样子
and just the way he held me so close and the way he was looking into my eyes....
我觉得他对我绝对有意思
I just definitely felt something.
是啊  从眼神能看出多少呢
But how much can you tell from a look?
不  我是从屁股感觉到的  我能感觉到
No. I felt it on my hip. I could tell.
宾  二十分钟后打壁球
Yo,Bing! Racquetball in 20 minutes.
乔伊  好兄弟  举起我的手  赏她一巴掌
Joey,be a pal. Lift up my hand and smack her with it.
-瑞秋  别回头看  -什么
- Oh,Rachel! Don't look. - What?
别担心  没什么大不了  我今晚有约会
C'mon you guys, I don't care, I have a date tonight.
你有约会
You have a date?
是的  莫妮卡为我安排的
Yeah, Monica's settin' me up.
那罗斯跟...
What about Ross and....
什么  我醋劲大发的事吗
What? My whole insane jealousy thing?
虽然那还挺有趣的
Well,you know,as much fun as that was...
我决定恢复常态
... I've decided to opt for sanity.
你真的不介意他们俩在一起了
You're okay about all this?
是的  日子还得过呢
Oh,yeah,come on! I'm moving on.
他爱怎么把她压在那扇窗上  就怎么压吧
He can press her up against that window as much as he wants.
我才不管  他干脆把她摔过窗子得了
For all I care,he can throw her through the damn thing.
各位
Hi,guys.
莫妮卡  我明早过来拿喵喵以前的猫玩具
Monica,I'll come by tomorrow and pick up Fluffy's old cat toys,okay?
不讲全名就不给喔
If you say his full name.
我明天可不可以过来拿喵喵膨膨的猫玩具
Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toys?
没问题
All right.
-你要养猫吗  -事实上  是我们要养猫
- You're getting a cat? - Actually,we're getting a cat.
一起养
Together?
你们两个  一起养
Both of you? Together?
我们准备让它一半时间跟罗斯住  一半跟我住
Yeah, we figure it'll live with Ross half the time, and with me half the time.
那多开心啊
Well,isn't that just lovely?
那是一件你们两个
That's something the two of you will be able to enjoy
可以疼爱非常非常久的东西
...for a really,really,really long time.
希望如此
Hopefully.
时间到了  我得走了  我有约会
Look at that. I gotta go! I got a date!
跟个男人
With a man.
祝各位今晚愉快
You guys have a really good night...
而你们两个会养一只好猫
...and you two have a really good cat.
顺手牵羊是不对的
We're not supposed to take these when we leave.
不晓得莫妮卡有没有告诉你
I don't know if Monica told you,
这是我离婚之后的第一次约会
but this is my first date since my divorce.
如果我看上去有一点紧张
If I seem a little nervous...
那是真的
... I am.
猫能活多久
How long do cats live?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
猫  能活多久
Cats. How long do they live?
如果不把它们丢到巴士下面的话
Figuring you don't throw them under a bus or something?
大概是十五六年吧
Maybe 15,16 years.
真是太好了
Well,that's just great.
干杯
Cheers!
好  碰杯
Right. Clink.
我本人没有莫妮卡介绍的招人喜欢  对不对
Monica told you I was cuter than this,didn't she?
不  麦克  不是你的问题  抱歉
No,Michael,it's not you. Sorry. It's just....
是我有心事
It's this thing.
可能事实没那么糟
It's probably not as bad as it sounds
我有一个朋友  他跟他的女友要养猫
... but this friend of mine is getting a cat with his girlfriend.
还真是...
Oh,that does sound....
他们两个才刚开始交往不久
He just started going out with her.
你和他交往过吗
Is this guy an old boyfriend?
他想得美
Yeah,he wishes.
对不起  你瞧瞧我
I'm sorry. Look at me.
-好了  麦克  谈谈你吧  -好
- Michael,let's talk about you. - All right.
那么
So....
以前你跟女友一起养过宠物吗
Did you ever get a pet with a girlfriend?
-我猜透原因了  -什么原因
- So I figured it out. - What?
史考特不想跟我上床的原因
Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me.
因为我不够性感
It's 'cause I'm not sexy enough.
菲比  别傻了
Phoebe,that's crazy.
第一次看到你之后  你知道我对钱德勒说什么吗
When I first met you,you know what I said to Chandelar?
我说"前凸后翘  有看头"
I said,"Excellent butt,great rack."
真的吗  嘴好甜
Really? That's so sweet.
说实在的  我很生气  可也很开心
I mean,I'm officially offended. But that's so sweet.
菲比  你想知道原因的话  必须开口去问他
If you wanna know what the deal is,you're gonna have to ask him.
你说得对  你说得对
You're right. You're right.
你真"可口"
You are so "yum"!
那是只猫  你知道的  是只猫
I mean,it's a cat,you know? It's a cat.
他们为什么不养只昆虫  养只果蝇就好了
Why can't they get a bug? One of those fruit flies.
那种只活一两天的东西
Those things that live for a day.
它们叫什么
What are they called?
果蝇
Fruit flies?
没错  谢谢
Yes. Thank you.
先生  要不要甜点
Sir, would you like dessert?
不  不要了
No. No dessert.
我想结账  拜托
Just the check. Please.
你这顿饭吃得不开心  是吗
Oh,no. You're not having fun,are you?
不  我很开心
No,no,I am.
但刚才一个半小时我都在回忆电影《餐馆》的情节
But because for the last hour and a half I've been playing the movie Diner in my head.
你看我
Oh,look at me.
Look at me.
我在跟一个很优秀的男人约会
I'm on a date with a really great guy.
却满脑子都是罗斯
All I can think about is Ross...
跟他的猫
...and his cat...
还有他的朱莉
...and his Julie.
我只想忘了他  天啊  我怎么做不到
I just want to get over him. gosh, why can't I do that?
听我说  我经历过离婚  相信我  你会好起来的
Look,I've been through a divorce. Trust me,you're gonna be fine.
你还看不出来  因为你跟他还没有了结
You can't see it because you haven't had closure
了结
Closure!
就是那个  我就需要那个
That's what it is! That's what I need!
天啊  你太厉害了
God,you're brilliant!
我怎么没想到  我要怎么了结
Why didn't I think of that? How do I get that?
这没有特定的方法  你只要...
Well,there's no one way really,it's just....
你只要想办法最终让他知道
Whatever it takes so that you can finally say to him:
"我不在乎你了"
"I'm over you."
不在乎你
Over you.
就是这样
That's what it is.
了结
Closure.
抱歉
Hello? Excuse me?
Excuse me. Hel
-稍等  -打断一下
- Hang on. - Excuse me?
-什么 -对不起
- What? - Hi. I'm sorry.
我需要跟你借一下电话
I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.
-我正在讲  -看得出来
- I'm talking. - I can see that.
我只打一通电话  很快  我还会付钱给你
One phone call,I'll be very quick. I'll even pay for it myself.
你对你的电话有点怪怪的
Ok. You're being a little weird about your phone.
我待会儿回电给你
I'll call you back.
谢了
Thank you.
答录机
Machine.
-我在等哔声  -很好
- Just waiting for the beep. - Good.
罗斯  我是瑞秋
Ross! Hi,it's Rachel.
我只是打来说
I'm just calling to say that...
一切都很好
...everything's fine.
我很为你
And I'm really happy for you...
和你的猫感到高兴
...and your cat.
对了  我认为你该给它起名叫麦克
Who,by the way,I think you should name Michael.
你看  我在想名字
And you know, you see there,I'm thinking of names...
所以显然我不在乎你了
...so obviously I am over you.
我不在乎你了
I am over you.
这就是我那位朋友所谓的"了结"
And that,my friend,is what they call "closure."
不不不
No, no, no...
莫妮卡  今天是星期天早上  星期天我绝不跑步
Monica, it's Sunday morning.  I'm not running on a Sunday.
-为什么  -因为是星期天
- Why not? - Because it's Sunday!
是神的日子
It's God's day.
你说停  我们就停
If you say stop,then we stop.
停
Stop.
不  别这样  我们不能停
No,come on! We can't stop!
还有三磅要减
We got three more pounds to go!
我是活力火车  而你在车上
I am the energy train and you are on board!
瑞秋
Hey Rach.
你的约会怎么样
And how was the date?
我记得有家餐厅
I think there was a restaurant.
我还记得有酒
I know there was wine.
事实上  朱莉在楼下叫出租车
Actually, Julie's downstairs getting a cab,
我想要拿猫玩具  莫妮卡有没有说
I just need the cat toys. Did Monica say....
你为什么那样看我
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
对不起  我不知道
I'm sorry. I don't know,I....
我觉得我昨晚好像梦到你
I feel like I dreamed about you last night...
但我不记得了
... but I don't remember.
那好吧
Ok.
在这儿
There they are.
我们昨晚通过电话吗  你有没有打给我
Did we speak on the phone last night? Did you call me?
没有  我昨晚住在朱莉家
No. I stayed at Julie's last night.
我还没回过家  你介意我听一下留言吗
Oh, actually I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?
随便
Oh,yeah,go ahead.
瑞秋  我有你的留言
Rach,I got a message from you!
麦克是谁
Who's Michael?
天啊
Oh,my God!
罗斯  别听  快挂了  电话给我
Ross,no! Hang up the phone. Give me the phone!
电话给我...
Give me the. . .
你不在乎我了
You're over me?
天啊
Oh,God!
-你  -我的天啊
- You're - Oh,God.
你不在乎我了
You're over me?
你是什么时候
When were you...
在乎我的
... under me?
瑞秋  瑞秋  你...
Rach. Rachel,do you...?
你之前在乎我吗
I mean,were you?
怎么回事
What?
基本上
Basically...
最近我...
...Lately,I've....
我对你有点感觉
I've sort of had feelings for you.
你对我有感觉
You've had feelings for me?
那又怎样  你先对我有感觉的
So? You had feelings for me first!
你知道我...  对你...
You know about my...I mean, you know I had...
你知道?
You know?
钱德勒告诉我的
Chandler told me.
钱德勒  什么时候  什么时候  什么时候
Chandler. When did he? When did he? When did he?
-你在中国的时候  -中国
- When you were in China. - China.
-认识朱莉时  -朱莉
- Meeting Julie. - Julie.
朱莉  那...  天啊
Julie. That's Oh,God!
朱莉  好  我需要躺下来
Julie, right. OK, I need to lie down.
不  你知道  我要站着
No,I'm gonna stand.
我要站着
I'm gonna stand...
我要走走  我走走  而且我站着
...and I'm gonna walk. I'm walking and I am standing.
现在你不在乎我了
Now you're over me?
你还在乎我吗
Are you over me?
那是朱莉  朱莉
That's Julie.Julie, Julie.
-朱莉  -亲爱的  出租车在等着
- Hi,Julie. - Hi, honey, I've got a cab waiting.
我马上下来
I'll be right down!
等等  你要走了
Wait,so you're going?
对  我得走  我现在没有办法谈这事
Well,okay,I have to. I can't deal with this right now.
出租车在等着
I mean,I've You know,I've got a cab.
我有女朋友  我要去领养一只猫
I've got a girlfriend. I'm gonna go get a cat.
好  好
OK, OK.
猫
Cat!
-乔伊  -菲比
- Hey,Joey. - Hey,Pheebs.
你为什么在看犹太教士弹电吉他
How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?
我找不到遥控器
I can't find the remote.
谢谢
Thank you.
对了  史考特约我去他家午餐  我去了
So, Scott asked me to come over for lunch today and I did.
-然后呢  -我们做了
- And? - And we did.
不错啊  菲比  好样的
All right, Phoebs, way to go
我好棒
Yea,me!
怎么发生的
So how did it happen?
我听了你的建议  问他到底怎么回事
Well, I finally took your advice and asked him what was going on.
那他说什么
What did he say?
他能理解性对女人而言
He said that, um, he understands how sex can be like,
可能会引起情绪波动
a very emotional thing for a woman
他只是怕我会开始胡思乱想
And he was just afraid that I was going to get all:
"他第二天会联系我吗"和"我们会有结果吗"
"Is he gonna call me the next day?" and "Where is this going?"
所以他说他想等他准备开始认真了再说
So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be serious.
所以我说"尽管放轻松"
So I said,"Okay. Relax,please."
性可以只是两个人一时的感觉
I mean, sex can be just about two people right there in the moment.
他要想再见我  可以打电话给我  不想也没关系
If he wants to see me again,he can call. If not,that's fine too.
所以在长谈之后
So after a lot of talking...
我说服他了
... I convinced him.
让我先搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
他让你求他跟你上床
He got you to beg to sleep with him.
他让你主动说  他永远不用再打电话给你
He got you to say he never has to call you again.
而且还让你觉得这是个好主意
And he got you thinking this is a great idea?
我对他佩服得五体投地
This man is my god!
我没有领养猫
I didn't get a cat.
真有趣
That's interesting.
不  一点都不有趣  非常非常不有趣
No, no, it's not interesting. OK, it's very, very not interesting.
百分之百不有趣  瑞秋
In fact it's actually 100 percent completely opposite of interesting.
好  我懂了  罗斯
Alright, I got it Ross.
你没有权利告诉我说  你喜欢过我
You had no right to say you ever had feelings for me.
什么
What?
在我发现之前  我跟朱莉过得很快乐
I was doing great with Julie before I found that about you!
在我发现之前  我也过得很快乐
I was doing great before I found that about you!
你以为看你跟朱莉那样  我心里好受吗
You think it's easy for me to see you with Julie?
你应该在我认识她之前说出来
You should've said something before I met her!
那时我不知道  那你为什么从没对我表白
I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything to me?
我从来没机会说出口
There was never a good time.
对  你只有一年机会  况且我们每晚都在一起
Right, you, you only had a year. We only hung out every night.
不是
Not...
每晚
...every night.
而且我也不是没试过  瑞秋
You know, and... and it's not like I didn't try, Rachel,
但每次都有状况发生
but things got in the way, y'know?
像是意大利人
Like ltalian guys...
或是前任未婚夫
...or ex-fiances...
或是意大利人
...or ltalian guys.
只有一个意大利人  你到底有没有重点
There was one Italian guy,okay? And do you have a point?
重点是  我现在已经不需要这样了
The point is,I don't need this right now!
太迟了
Okay? It's too late.
我在跟别人交往  我很快乐  我这艘船起航了
I'm with somebody else. I'm happy. This ship has sailed!
你就这么撇开对我的感情了吗
Yeah, what're you saying, you just sort of put away feelings or whatever the hell it was you felt for me?
我从九年级就开始这样了  我早驾轻就熟了
Hey, I've been doin' it since the ninth grade, I've gotten pretty damn good at it.
那好  那你说撇就撇吧  罗斯
Alright, fine, you go ahead and you do that, alright Ross.
我才不要你这艘破船
Cause I don't need your stupid ship.
-好  -好
- Good. - Good!
你知道吗  我现在了结了
And you know what? Now I got closure!
试试底下那个
Try the bottom one.
莫妮卡  现在是早上六点半
Monica,it's 6:30 in the morning.
我们不去锻炼了  结束了
We're not working out. It's over.
别啊  只剩一磅了  别泄气
No way! With one pound to go? Come on!
我们锻炼  我们运动  我们在其中舞动
We're workin',we're movin' We're in the zone,we're groovin'
我不在乎我的最后一磅
I don't mind the last pound.
我很喜欢这最后一磅
In fact,I kind of like the last pound.
所以别逼我做我会后悔的事
So don't make me do anything that I'll regret.
那你要做什么  肥仔
What you gonna do,fat boy?
怎么了
What?
没事  只想告诉你  我觉得你精力这么充沛真棒
Nothing. Except tell you I think it's wonderful how much energy you have.
谢了
Well,thanks.
尤其是在你眼下找工作那么困难的情况下
Especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.
你不能告诉你父母你被开除了
You can't tell your parents you were fired,
因为他们会失望
because they'd be disappointed.
要是你有个男朋友  还可以借个肩膀让你哭
And it's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.
是没有  但是我...
Well,no. But I....
换做是我的话  我都没有动力下床了
If it were me, I'd have difficulty getting out of bed at all.
我努力保持乐观
You know,I try to stay positive.
那你...
So you....
你想出去跑会儿步吗
You feel like going for a run?
好吧
All right.
你不一定要去跑的  你可以在这里睡一下
Because you don't have to. If you want, you could just take a nap right here.
-好  只睡一小会儿 -好
- OK. Just for a little while - Okey.